作词 : mpi
作曲 : Hiroyuki Sawano
Oh Take a look in the mirror you look so sad
镜子里的你 看上去那么悲伤
It's so cold like that winter market we used to go
寒冷的感觉 如同我们曾经常去的冬季市场
I don't cry anymore but I feel so hurt
我不会再哭了 可是悲伤却未曾减少
So I don't need you to close to me
所以我不需要你在身边
You don't hear me so you said
你未曾听到我说什么 所以你说
I don't know why things have changed since yesterday
我不知道为什么 从昨天起 一切都已改变
This could be love again
那大概就是再次爱上你吧
All I need is you
我想要的 只有你
Comeback, I'm waiting, Anytime
回来吧 无论何时 我都在等待着你
The heavy rains come
大雨倾泻而下
Still I miss days with you
而我仍怀念着 你一同度过的时光
I can't look into your face
我不敢再面对你
Oh Feeling blue and looking back again
回首往事 悲恸将我湮没
Please come back to me
回到我的身边吧 求求你
Oh Take a look in the mirror you look so sad
镜子里的你 看上去那么悲伤
It's so cold like that winter market we used to go
寒冷的感觉 如同我们曾经常去的冬季市场
I don't cry anymore but I feel so hurt
我不会再哭了 可是悲伤却未曾减少
So I don't need you to close to me
所以我不需要你在身边
You don't hear me so you said
你未曾听到我说什么 所以你说
I don't know why things have changed since yesterday
我不知道为什么 从昨天起 一切都已改变
This could be love again
那大概就是再次爱上你吧
All I need is you
我想要的 只有你
Comeback, I'm waiting, Anytime
回来吧 无论何时 我都在等待着你
The heavy rains come
大雨倾泻而下
Still I miss days with you
而我仍怀念着 你一同度过的时光
I can't look into your face
我不敢再面对你
Oh Feeling blue and looking back again
回首往事 悲恸将我湮没
Please come back to me
回到我的身边吧 求求你
To stay with you always
想要永远和你厮守
You're the world to me, and dreaming on
你是我的全部 是我梦的延续
So you can take my sword for you
所以让我成为你的力量吧
oh How do you feel, so fine
现在 感觉好点了吗
You're the world to me, and dream on
你是我的全部 是我梦的延续
You stole my heart so long ago
很久以前 你就偷走了我的心
Oh I release my soul
所以我释放了 我的灵魂
So you feel my song
于是你感受到 我的心声